<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Welcome To Metricly</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Welcome To Metricly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda Cost—Your Guide to Understand, Calculate, and Optimize</title>
      <link>/aws-lambda-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-lambda-cost/</guid>
      <description>In this article we’ll help you get an understanding of AWS Lambda cost, and how it is calculated. More specifically, we’ll cover the relationships between configuration and cost and help you build strategies to optimize both cost and performance.
Since its release four years ago, AWS Lambda has enabled organizations to move their applications into a serverless architecture. The ability to build a system made up of small, on-demand units of functionality is especially appealing to companies that want to increase scalability and reduce costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies With Metric Conditions Now More Flexible</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/policies-with-metric-conditions-now-more-flexible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/policies-with-metric-conditions-now-more-flexible/</guid>
      <description>When building a policy that contains multiple metric conditions, users can now use the Match Conditions feature to toggle between validating all of the conditions listed or just any one condition provided. Previously, policies with multiple metric conditions only fired when all listed conditions were met.
How Policies Fire Using All vs Any:
 All: Policy only fires an alert when all metric conditions are met Any: Policy fires an alert when at least one metric condition is met  Note that this Match Conditions feature is only available with metric conditions, and is found in the conditions tab in the Policy Editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EC2 Instance Types—6 Things You Need To Know Before Selecting</title>
      <link>/ec2-instance-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ec2-instance-types/</guid>
      <description>When an organization and its engineers begin their first forays into Amazon’s Elastic Computing (EC2) solutions, the selection of the right EC2 instance type may appear to be an easy decision based on capability and cost. Early decisions might be made based on:
 Processor type and count Available memory Cost  For a quick prototype or a single-instance solution, this may be all that you need to consider, but as your cloud footprint increases and you begin investing in additional EC2 instances, you should consider additional factors which aren’t well known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Pricing API—How to Use It to Predict and Control AWS Costs</title>
      <link>/aws-pricing-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-pricing-api/</guid>
      <description>About The AWS Pricing API Determining the exact price of an AWS service is a particularly important (and notoriously challenging) step in predicting and controling AWS costs. To help with this task, the AWS pricing API was introduced at the end of 2015.
Amazon released the API in response to requests from partners and customers for a programmatic way to access AWS pricing information. Consumers can access the pricing index and locate pricing information for specific services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Maintenance Mode</title>
      <link>/improved-maint-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/improved-maint-mode/</guid>
      <description>In the past, users had to manually end maintenance mode for elements in their inventory. Now, you can set a maintenance duration that expires on its own! This means you won’t have to worry about remembering to re-activate your element monitoring. It also saves you quite a few clicks in the UI.
Check it out:
Things to Remember About Maintenance Mode:
 Checks and metrics sent by elements in maintenance mode are not evaluated for the attached policies and alerts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/demo/lambda-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/demo/lambda-request/</guid>
      <description>Beta: AWS Lambda Sizing Tool We&#39;re launching a set of tools for AWS Lambda sizing and reporting! Help shape Metricly&#39;s tools by test-driving pre-release versions and letting us know what you think.
 Beta: AWS Lambda Sizing Tool We&#39;re launching a set of tools for AWS Lambda sizing and reporting! Help shape Metricly&#39;s tools by test-driving pre-release versions and letting us know what you think.
 Join the beta program By joining, you&#39;ll get free early access to the tool in return for your feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cost Tool</title>
      <link>/aws-cost-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-cost-tool/</guid>
      <description>[features=&#34;total-cost-dashboard&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/dashboard.svg); } [features=&#34;aws-services-cost&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/pie-chart.svg); } [features=&#34;ec2-recommendation&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/ec2-sizing.svg); } [features=&#34;boxplot-report&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/boxplot-report.svg); } .aws-head .row:before { content: &#34;&#34;; position: absolute; left: 100px; background-image: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/test-hero.png); width: 300px; height: 300px; background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: contain; } .aws-head .row:after { content: &#34;&#34;; position: absolute; right: 100px; background-image: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/test-right.png); width: 300px; height: 300px; background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: contain; } @media only screen and (max-width: 1450px) { .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cost Tool</title>
      <link>/aws-sizing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-sizing-tool/</guid>
      <description>Using Metricly&#39;s AWS Sizing Tool Achieve instance-level AWS cost savings without compromising on performance. Try 21 Days Free Skip To Guide    Using Our AWS Sizing Tool  Rightsizing Your EC2s Monitoring The Changes Create an Ongoing Strategy    AWS Sizing is Confusing Setting up the right instance when there are over 400,000 unique EC2 SKUs (products) to choose from doesn&#39;t just sound like a challenge–it is one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back-end Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/back-end-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/back-end-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based adaptive monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of your environment to optimize your resource allocation, reduce your cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to your business.
About The Job The ideal candidate has experience developing distributed Java -based applications running on AWS and enjoys the challenges associated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Monitoring Ebook</title>
      <link>/ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ebook/</guid>
      <description>Free Ebook Cloud Monitoring as a Service Here&#39;s what you get in this 12-page essential guide:
Industry best-practices Importance of machine learning in monitoring Understand anomaly detection Match performance with capacity Cloud cost analysis           Download your copy now  Are you struggling to understand cloud monitoring? There are countless options to choose from including enterprise, open-source, and SaaS solutions. In this eBook, we’ll walk you through how and why to use cloud monitoring as a service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Specialist</title>
      <link>/careers/content-marketing-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/content-marketing-specialist/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based machine learning monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
About The Job This is an opportunity to join a high-growth technology company that offers a software as a service product founded on a unique technology resulting from a decade of R&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Policy</title>
      <link>/legal/cookie-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/cookie-policy/</guid>
      <description>Effective [September 28th], 2018
Metricly (&amp;ldquo;Metricly&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) respects individual privacy and value the confidence of its customers and business partners. As such, Metricly is committed to upholding the highest ethical standards in its business practices
This Cookie Policy (&amp;ldquo;Policy&amp;rdquo;) applies to this website or to any website or application that includes a link or reference to this Policy (together, the &amp;ldquo;Site(s)&amp;rdquo;) and describes what cookies are, what types of cookies are placed on your device when you visit the Site and how we use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EC2 Instances</title>
      <link>/ec2-instances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ec2-instances/</guid>
      <description>The Ultimate Guide to EC2 Instances In this guide we tackle 9 different EC2 topics, ranging from beginner to advanced, to provide you with the ultimate resource for long-term success. Feel free to skip around or dive right in at the start!
Updated on Nov 28, 2018           The Basics of EC2 1. What is an EC2 instance? 2. EC2 Instance Pricing Options 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/front-end-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/front-end-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based adaptive monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of your environment to optimize your resource allocation, reduce your cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to your business. To learn more and start a free trial, visit: www.metricly.com.
Our Stack  Amazon Web Services, Docker Cassandra, Elasticsearch, Kafka, Redis, Spark Java 8, Spring Boot, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licenses</title>
      <link>/legal/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/licenses/</guid>
      <description>Metricly uses and promotes the use of certain third-party and open source technology (&amp;ldquo;Third Party Software&amp;rdquo;), primarily data collection agents and other tools (&amp;ldquo;Agents&amp;rdquo;), for use with the Metricly Service. Any Agents provided by Metricly utilizing Third Party Software are governed by the applicable license, including open source licenses. If there are provisions in such licenses that conflict with the applicable Metricly Terms, the relevant Third Party Software license terms will apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixbook</title>
      <link>/customers/mixbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/mixbook/</guid>
      <description>Back to Stories customer story Mixbook Achieves “High Level of Confidence” in AWS Monitoring Feautured commentator Robert Butler - Senior DevOps Engineer, Uptime Lead and Product Owner      About Industry
SaaS, Print
 Company size
51-200
 Headquarters
Redwood City, CA
   Objective  Automate infrastructure monitoring to meet the demand of a diverse and highly scalable environment.
 Success Monitoring that automatically learns the behaviour of metrics and newly added resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring</title>
      <link>/monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monitoring/</guid>
      <description>[features=&#34;tv-projection&#34;] h4:before { content: &#34;&#34;; } [features=&#34;flexible-dashboard&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/flexible-dashboard.svg); } [features=&#34;ad-hoc-graphing&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/ad-hoc-graphing.svg); } [features=&#34;tv-projection&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/tv-projection.svg); } [features=&#34;sudden-change&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/sudden-change.svg); } [features=&#34;metric-bands&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/metric-bands.svg); } [features=&#34;multiple-conditions&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/multiple-conditions.svg); } [features=&#34;pre-configured-policies&#34;] h4:before { content: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/icons/monitoring/pre-configured.svg); } .monitoring .aws-head { background: #2D516C; } .aws-head .row:before { content: &#34;&#34;; position: absolute; left: 100px; background-image: url(/wp-content/uploads/assets/graphics/features/monitoring-left.svg); width: 300px; height: 300px; background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: contain; } .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oomnitza</title>
      <link>/customers/oomnitza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/oomnitza/</guid>
      <description>Back to Stories customer story Oomnitza Saves 15% on AWS Costs Using Metricly Feautured commentator
Jon Burt - Director of Engineering
     About Industry
SaaS
 Company size
11-50
 Headquarters
San Francisco, CA
   Objective Control rising AWS spending without compromising the overall performance.  Success AWS bill reduced by 15% from EC2 sizing reccomendations, while maintaining performance.  Product Uses  AWS Cost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paid Terms of Service</title>
      <link>/legal/terms-service-paid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/terms-service-paid/</guid>
      <description>Metricly, Inc.
SERVICE AGREEMENT
(Software-as-a-Service)
SERVICE SUMMARY
 1. Terms of Use. This Service Summary outlines the services to be provided under this agreement. Customer agrees that Customer&amp;rsquo;s access to and use of the Service (as defined in Section 3 below) shall at all times be subject to the Metricly, Inc. (&amp;ldquo;Metricly&amp;rdquo;) Terms of Use, which can be found in Exhibit A. This Service Summary and the Metricly Terms of Use are referred to collectively as the &amp;ldquo;Service Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patents</title>
      <link>/patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/patents/</guid>
      <description>Concurrent Learning and Performance Information Processing System Patent numbers:
5,835,902 &amp;amp; 6,289,330
Multi-Kernel Neural Network Concurrent Learning, Monitoring &amp;amp; Forecasting System Patent numbers:
6,216,119 &amp;amp; 6,647,377
Automatic Data Extraction, Error Correction and Forecasting System Patent numbers:
6,591,255
Enhanced Computer Performance Forecasting System Patent numbers:
6,876,988
Engine Analyzer and Configuration Utility used in a Computer Performance Forecasting System / Automated Analyzers for Estimation Systems Patent numbers:
7,127,439
Computer Performance Estimation System Configured to Take Expected Events into Consideration Patent numbers:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Support Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/platform-support-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/platform-support-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that helps organizations monitor the cost, capacity and performance of application infrastructure hosted in a public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
We are headquartered in Reston VA (Washington D.C. area) with remote employees in multiple US states and countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Premier Services</title>
      <link>/premier-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/premier-services/</guid>
      <description>Premier Services The Fast Track to Success Your mission is to save; we’re here to help. Each subscription to Metricly comes with Premier Services so you can focus on your optimization goals.
Contact Sales      About Premier Services Premier Services is a set of free resources included in your subscription to Metricly. We offer these services because we believe in our product and in your potential to save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Pick Your Metricly Plan  Cost Management $5/month Per Host
 OS Metrics Collection Cost Analysis Reports Sizing Reccomendations Emailed Reports 65+ Integrations Metric Dashboards &amp; Graphing Anomaly Detection Alerts &amp; Checks REST API Metrics Ingestion  Get Started    Cost Management $10/month Per Host
 OS Metrics Collection Cost Analysis Reports Sizing Reccomendations Emailed Reports 65+ Integrations Metric Dashboards &amp; Graphing Anomaly Detection Alerts &amp; Checks REST API Metrics Ingestion  Get Started    All Features $15/month Per Host</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Metricly has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website (www.metricly.com).
If you have questions or wish to opt-out, you can contact us at the following:
Metricly, Inc.
12700 Sunrise Valley Drive, 2nd Floor
Reston, VA 20191
USA
Email: metricly@metricly.com
Metricly&amp;rsquo;s Privacy practices at a Glance    Purpose Lawful Basis Relevant Personal Information Retention period     Provision of our Services, including delivering the Site, responding to your support tickets, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Administrator</title>
      <link>/careers/sales-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/sales-administrator/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that leverages advanced analytics and proactive customer support to help organizations safely and easily reduce their public cloud spending. The service offering monitors the cost, capacity, and performance of modern infrastructure hosted in public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to recommend savings, optimize resource allocation, and identify performance bottlenecks that matter to businesses of all sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signup</title>
      <link>/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup/</guid>
      <description> 21-Day Free Trial Full access. No credit card required.
  Work Email     Password        Full Name        Password        Confirm password     I agree to the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.    Create account  Already a user? Log in          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Content Specialist</title>
      <link>/careers/technical-content-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/technical-content-specialist/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based machine learning monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
About The Job This is an opportunity to join a high-growth technology company that offers a software as a service product founded on a unique technology resulting from a decade of R&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trial Terms of Service</title>
      <link>/legal/terms-service-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/terms-service-trial/</guid>
      <description>Metricly, Inc.
FREE SERVICE AGREEMENT
(HOSTED ARRANGEMENT)
 THIS SERVICE SUMMARY AND ACCOMPANYING TERMS OF USE ARE PROVIDED FOR INFORMATION PURPOSES ONLY. 
PRIOR TO BEING GRANTED ACCESS TO THE SERVICE, CUSTOMER WILL BE REQUIRED TO ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS FREE SERVICE AGREEMENT, INCLUSIVE OF THIS SERVICE SUMMARY AND THE TERMS OF USE.
SERVICE SUMMARY
1. Terms of Use. This Service Summary outlines the services to be provided under this free services agreement (the &amp;ldquo;Free Service Agreement&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX Designer</title>
      <link>/careers/ui-ux-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/ui-ux-designer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that helps organizations monitor the cost, capacity and performance of application infrastructure hosted in a public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
The company is headquartered in Reston VA (Washington D.C. area) with remote employees in multiple US states and countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewpost</title>
      <link>/customers/viewpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/viewpost/</guid>
      <description>Back to Stories customer story Viewpost Gets Insights To Cut AWS Cost in&amp;nbsp;Half Featured commentators
Lawrence “LT” Telfort - Systems Administrator
Shawn Strickland - Operations Manager      About Industry
SaaS, Finance
 Company size
51-200
 Headquarters
Maitland, FL
   Objective To get visibility into gaps of AWS resources cost, and find performance-safe savings.
 Success Clarity of AWS costs, right-sized EC2 instances, and actionable performance alerting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>