<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Compass by Metricly on Welcome To Metricly</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Compass by Metricly on Welcome To Metricly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda Cost—Your Guide to Understand, Calculate, and Optimize</title>
      <link>/aws-lambda-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-lambda-cost/</guid>
      <description>In this article we’ll help you get an understanding of AWS Lambda cost, and how it is calculated. More specifically, we’ll cover the relationships between configuration and cost and help you build strategies to optimize both cost and performance.
Since its release four years ago, AWS Lambda has enabled organizations to move their applications into a serverless architecture. The ability to build a system made up of small, on-demand units of functionality is especially appealing to companies that want to increase scalability and reduce costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies With Metric Conditions Now More Flexible</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/policies-with-metric-conditions-now-more-flexible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/policies-with-metric-conditions-now-more-flexible/</guid>
      <description>When building a policy that contains multiple metric conditions, users can now use the Match Conditions feature to toggle between validating all of the conditions listed or just any one condition provided. Previously, policies with multiple metric conditions only fired when all listed conditions were met.
How Policies Fire Using All vs Any:
 All: Policy only fires an alert when all metric conditions are met Any: Policy fires an alert when at least one metric condition is met  Note that this Match Conditions feature is only available with metric conditions, and is found in the conditions tab in the Policy Editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EC2 Instance Types—6 Things You Need To Know Before Selecting</title>
      <link>/ec2-instance-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ec2-instance-types/</guid>
      <description>When an organization and its engineers begin their first forays into Amazon’s Elastic Computing (EC2) solutions, the selection of the right EC2 instance type may appear to be an easy decision based on capability and cost. Early decisions might be made based on:
 Processor type and count Available memory Cost  For a quick prototype or a single-instance solution, this may be all that you need to consider, but as your cloud footprint increases and you begin investing in additional EC2 instances, you should consider additional factors which aren’t well known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Pricing API—How to Use It to Predict and Control AWS Costs</title>
      <link>/aws-pricing-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-pricing-api/</guid>
      <description>About The AWS Pricing API Determining the exact price of an AWS service is a particularly important (and notoriously challenging) step in predicting and controling AWS costs. To help with this task, the AWS pricing API was introduced at the end of 2015.
Amazon released the API in response to requests from partners and customers for a programmatic way to access AWS pricing information. Consumers can access the pricing index and locate pricing information for specific services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Maintenance Mode</title>
      <link>/improved-maint-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/improved-maint-mode/</guid>
      <description>In the past, users had to manually end maintenance mode for elements in their inventory. Now, you can set a maintenance duration that expires on its own! This means you won’t have to worry about remembering to re-activate your element monitoring. It also saves you quite a few clicks in the UI.
Check it out:
Things to Remember About Maintenance Mode:
 Checks and metrics sent by elements in maintenance mode are not evaluated for the attached policies and alerts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>