<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Careers on Welcome To Metricly</title>
    <link>/careers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Careers on Welcome To Metricly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/careers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back-end Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/back-end-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/back-end-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based adaptive monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of your environment to optimize your resource allocation, reduce your cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to your business.
About The Job The ideal candidate has experience developing distributed Java -based applications running on AWS and enjoys the challenges associated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Specialist</title>
      <link>/careers/content-marketing-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/content-marketing-specialist/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based machine learning monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
About The Job This is an opportunity to join a high-growth technology company that offers a software as a service product founded on a unique technology resulting from a decade of R&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/front-end-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/front-end-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based adaptive monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of your environment to optimize your resource allocation, reduce your cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to your business. To learn more and start a free trial, visit: www.metricly.com.
Our Stack  Amazon Web Services, Docker Cassandra, Elasticsearch, Kafka, Redis, Spark Java 8, Spring Boot, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Support Engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/platform-support-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/platform-support-engineer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that helps organizations monitor the cost, capacity and performance of application infrastructure hosted in a public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
We are headquartered in Reston VA (Washington D.C. area) with remote employees in multiple US states and countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Administrator</title>
      <link>/careers/sales-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/sales-administrator/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that leverages advanced analytics and proactive customer support to help organizations safely and easily reduce their public cloud spending. The service offering monitors the cost, capacity, and performance of modern infrastructure hosted in public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to recommend savings, optimize resource allocation, and identify performance bottlenecks that matter to businesses of all sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Content Specialist</title>
      <link>/careers/technical-content-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/technical-content-specialist/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based machine learning monitoring solution that helps organizations monitor cloud services, applications, infrastructure, and public cloud costs. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
About The Job This is an opportunity to join a high-growth technology company that offers a software as a service product founded on a unique technology resulting from a decade of R&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX Designer</title>
      <link>/careers/ui-ux-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/ui-ux-designer/</guid>
      <description>About Metricly Metricly is a SaaS-based solution that helps organizations monitor the cost, capacity and performance of application infrastructure hosted in a public cloud. Metricly&amp;rsquo;s advanced machine learning algorithms learn the behavior and workload patterns of environments to optimize resource allocation, reduce cloud spending, and identify performance anomalies that matter to businesses of all sizes.
The company is headquartered in Reston VA (Washington D.C. area) with remote employees in multiple US states and countries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>